Last time on Zombieland Saga Revenge, we somehow got back into doing the idol thing.
It started with a TV appearance where we co-hosted a segment with Saga's very own rock star, White Ryu.
Can you believe?
Saki is a longtime fan of his, so she kind of went nuts.
It might even be love. Oh my gosh!
Then Saki found out that Ryu's radio show might be ending, and she went even more nuts!
She confessed her feelings to him, and he opened up to her, too.
It was super touching!
And now Frank Shishu is in charge of his radio show, so Saga can be Saga!
We're gonna light the way for Saga's burning soul!
Such super tight choreography.
We're probably not at that level.
I think Kotaro's getting out of the bath now, so...
What's wrong?
There's nothing wrong at all!
I'm done!
So what kind of stuff were you looking up?
Just random things.
Hey, don't eat that!
It's not a thing!
That's for...
Crap time!
Drop it!
We're already exactly right.
Those people...
Whatever I say!
Why would you be thinking about this hair?
Something that she likes talking about?
Things that usually look pretty tough, nobody does.
They would not have seen one thought.
But what kind of stuff that you tell people the first thought is?
What kind of stuff do you try to do?